

#### Bharatkumar Laxman Odedra

Contact No.:- +91 9879690847 Email:- odedrabl1638@gmail.com Location:- Ahmedabad, Gujarat

### **Professional Summary**

In customer support 8+ years of experience working with GMMCO Limited a C.K. Birla company, in Engine Power Division dealing with Caterpillar industrial diesel engines and diesel generator sets with various kind of panel logic. Primarily focused on customer service segment like commissioning of new machines, trouble shooting of machines, create new business opportunity like annual maintenance contract, total maintenance and repair contract, operation and maintenance contract etc. Excellent interpersonal and communication abilities as a PSSR (Product Support Sales Representative) and possess a wide range of technical skills.

### **Work History**

## Manager Customer Support & PSSR Gujarat (April 2019 – Present)

- Looking after the allocated customer of whole Gujarat and taking care of corporate customer
  like Reliance industries, Essar steel, Nayara energy, Schott kaisha, Schott glass, Schneider
  electric, Piramal glass, Abg cement, Ultratech cement, Torrent Power, Thermax Limited, Srf
  Limited etc. to provide them timely service and parts and tracking the business opportunity
  from this corporate customer as well as small fleet customer of Gujarat.
- Handling the field engineers and time to time arranging the sessions with the field engineers to
  motivate them and to take the feedback from them about the ground problems and customer
  behavior.
- Providing operation and maintenance training to the corporate and small fleet customer with power point presentations at customer premises as well as on customer care meet held at Gmmco Limited end and spreading brand awareness to the customer by arranging meeting with the customers.
- Time to time updating the customer by educating them about the service offerings and about the new program launch by the company.
- Communicating with the head quarter team and leaders about the opportunity and the obstacles that are facing by the team and customer.

Functioning as a strong chain between the customer and Gmmco Limited.

# Deputy Manager Customer Support & PSSR Gujarat (October 2016- March 2019)

- Carry out technical audits of the Caterpillar industrial engines and generator sets and recommend accordingly to the customers.
- By regularly meeting the customer increasing the touch points to the small fleet customers as well as large fleet customers.
- Meeting the out of fold customers and by educating them bring in fold.
- Getting the wil-fitter information and collecting the competitor data from customer.
- Providing quotations of parts and services on time to time to the customers and made customer to remember when to take what kind of services for their engines and generator sets.

# Assistant Manager Customer Support & PSSR Gujarat (December 2013 – September 2016)

- Taking care of out of fold customers and small fleet customer of Gujarat
- Meeting the allocated customer and take the feedback from customer and collecting the customer data and work on it to understand the business opportunity and the obstacles.
- 4. Senior Engineer Customer Support (June 2011 October 2013)
- Responsible for the annual maintenance contract between reliance industries Jamnagar and Gmmco Limited.
- Taking care of other small fleet customers and providing timely preventive maintenance service, breakdown service, technical audits of the Caterpillar engines and generator sets.

### Skills

- High technical skill of Caterpillar engines and generator sets
- High communication skill and convincing power to the customer
- Good knowledge of Dealer Business System (DBS).
- Good computer knowledge of excel, word, and power point.
- Efficiently working in team.

#### Education

- Executive Program in Business Administration
   Department of Management Studies IIT Madras (2016 2018)
- B.Tech. in Electrical
   Nirma University Ahmedabad (2007 2011)
- Diploma in Electrical (2006)